<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>the hearse’s Personal Site on the hearse</title>
    <link>https://www.hearse.live/</link>
    <description>Recent content in the hearse’s Personal Site on the hearse</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 13:55:59 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.hearse.live/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Do not sign the RMS open letter</title>
      <link>https://www.hearse.live/posts/rms-support-letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 13:55:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hearse.live/posts/rms-support-letter/</guid>
      <description>It is disappointing to see the sheer amount of hate, immaturity and discontent towards RMS in the recent return to FSF scandal. There is no Free software movement without Richard Stallman. You may not agree with everything he has ever expressed, but that is no reason to demand him to be put down. Discarding a man based on statements you disagree with, that have nothing to do with his message is dishonest and unbelievably disgusting. Please sign the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/rms-support-letter/rms-support-letter.github.io&#34;&gt;RMS support letter&lt;/a&gt; to give Richard Stallman support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using NetBSD on the desktop, personal notes for dwm and such</title>
      <link>https://www.hearse.live/posts/netbsd-desktop-common-problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jan 2021 13:55:59 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.hearse.live/posts/netbsd-desktop-common-problems/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Table of contents:  Useful NetBSD commands to get working installation with DWM To fix SSL errors with curl and git Good website to get sauce Get a good mirror dwm won&amp;rsquo;t compile  Use this command to find the missing file. NetBSD FreeBSD      Useful NetBSD commands to get working installation with DWM I might need this in the future, really don&amp;rsquo;t want to figure it out again and it&amp;rsquo;s good website-filler.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>